Barbara: Now, let’s go upstairs. Follow me. Be careful.
The ceiling is very low here.
Leo: It’s a very old house.
Barbara: Yes, the house is 300 years old.
My family lived here for nearly 80 years.
There are six bedrooms. This was my father’s bedroom.
Kim: Is there heat in the house?
Barbara: Yes, there is.
Why do you ask? Are you cold?
Kim: Yes, it’s very cold in here.
Leo: That’s because we’re from California.
Barbara: Let’s go and see the other bedrooms.
Leo: Yes, of course. ...
Well, what do you think, Kim? I love it! Don’t you?
Kim: I’m not sure. There’s something about the house I don’t like.
Leo: Kim, it’s perfect for the kids.
Think of the yard. And it’s a real authentic country house.
What do you say?
Kim: I suppose so. If you’re sure.
Leo: I am sure!
Miss…uh, Barbara. We want it. We want to rent the house.
Barbara: Excellent.
Leo: When can we move in?
Barbara: As soon as you like.